大家好，我是来自ugs团队的Hautchington。
hi everyone I'm hautchington from the ugs team
今天我演讲的题目是 "通往小麦的道路"。
today my talk title is fills road to wheat
我将会谈论
and I'm going to talk
关于新的ugs开发经验
about the new ugs developing experience
以小麦为中心
centered around wheat
首先让我快速介绍一下自己
let me quickly introduce myself first
我是view和vit两个团队的成员。
I'm a member of both the view and vit
卡团队的成员，是一名全职的开放歌曲开发者
card teams as a full time open songs developer
我的主要工作是为vgs开发曲子。
my main focus is on the tulings for vgs
所以
so
我维护并参与了几个与vgs项目有关的项目
I maintain and contribute to several projects related
我的主要工作是为vgs做准备，所以我维护和贡献了几个与vgs项目脚手架和捆绑有关的项目。
to vgs project scaffolding and bundling
最明显的是view cri fit和create view。
most notably view cri fit and create view
我的礼物用户名是在苏打茶
my gift username is at soda tea
我的微博账号是我的手机号
and my twitter handle is my phone name
在hotchinjang
at hotchinjang
今年早些时候
earlier this year
我们把好的老家的coi项目
we put the good oldville coi project
进入维护模式
into maintenance mode
意味着我们将不再
meaning that we will no longer
积极为其添加新功能
actively add new features to it
但它只是运回了一些修复功能
but it's only shipped back fixes
现在的官方建议是
now the official recommendation
是使用下面的命令来创建新的
is to use the following command to create new
project mpm create view at 3
projects mpm create view at 3
它比UCI要轻巧得多
it is much more lightweight than UCI
不需要额外的
requires no additional
全局安装工具，接受mpm和node
global installation of tools acceptful mpm and node
而且它一直是最新的
and it is always up to date
呃，最近我们还设法将其纳入
uh recently we also managed to incorporate it
纳入官方饲料模板
into the official feed templates
所以现在当你运行
so now when you run the
mpn create vitad latest 命令
mpn create vitad latest command
你就可以看到 呃
you will you can also see the uh
一个自定义的创建视图选项
a customized with create view option
旁边还有两个简约的
in the job John alongside the 2 minimalistic
模板。
templates provided by create wit
它将创建一个完全相同的项目
it will create the exact same project
和创建视图命令一样
as the create view command
和基于小麦的空载
and the airborne based on wheat
所以在今天的谈话中
so in today's talk
我将尝试为你回答这些问题
I'll try to answer these questions for you
首先，为什么我们的视图团队
first why do we the view team
决定从
decide to switch from
vapac到创建view和vit
vapac to create view and vit
究竟有哪些不同的方法？
exactly what are the different approaches
视图调整生态系统所采取的方法
the view tuning ecosystem is taken
在其中的一个领域
in an area of it
我们可以期待什么更有趣的新功能
what more interesting new features can we expect
在不久的将来，在
in the near future in the
视图生态系统
view ecosystem
第一个也是最显著的变化
the first and most notable change
是将我们的生态系统
is to turn our ecosystem
摆脱网络包的束缚
away from web pack
我不得不说，这需要一些勇气
I have to say that it takes some courage
和挣扎，我们
and struggle for us
做出这个决定
to make this decision
因为这样做，我们是在
because by doing so we are
基本上放弃了
essentially dropping
我们以前在网络包方面所做的大量努力
lots of our previous efforts devoted to the web pack
生态系统
ecosystem
但
but the
但现在维生素生态系统已经越来越成熟了
vit ecosystem is now getting more and more mature
我们相信这是值得的
and we believe it's worth it
效益是非常明显的，令人印象深刻
the benefits are very obvious and impressive
我们都知道
we all know that
合适的步骤服务器比白包快得多
fit step server is way faster than white packs
准确地说，是完全公平地结束
to be precise to end completely fair
好吧，这实际上是可能的
well it is actually possible
获得
to get the
几乎相同的性能，因为适合与湿包
nearly the same performance as fit with wet pack
只要你有
as long as you have
配置了
configured the
原生的比较工具，如swc或BS build
native comparison tools such as swc or BS build
而且你有一个非常好的
and you have a very good
现金考虑，而且是温暖的启动
cash considerations and it is a warm startup
然而，要获得所有这些配置是非常困难的
however it is extremely hard to get all these
配置的正确性
configurations right
而且它还会有大量的
and it will quite tons of
辩护
defendancies
同时，在适合
meanwhile in fit
良好的性能是开箱即用的
the good performance is out of the box
你不需要额外配置任何东西
you don't have to configure anything additionally
此外，当它涉及到热模型的更换
besides when it comes to the hot model replacement
功能时，时间
feature the time
访问执行的复杂性是恒定的
complexity of the visit implementation is constant
而网络黑客是专业的身体帐户
while web hacks is professional to the body account
因此，当项目增长的
so when the project grows the
部分现代替换在网络包
part modern replacement in web pack
变得更慢，而这是设计上的问题
gets slower and this is by design
这意味着web pack永远无法赶上它。
meaning that web pack can never catch up with it
它的另一个好处是它的简单性
another benefit of it is its simplicity
它的配置格式是简单而直观的
the configuration format of it is easy and intuitive
这样我们就不需要另一个抽象层了
so that we don't need another layer of abstraction
像web pack链一样，让用户轻松
like web pack chain to let the users easily
获得他们想要的配置，以适应
get their desired configurations in fit
甚至对于生态系统包的提供
and even for ecosystem package offers
它更容易从vitcom中扩展
it is easier to extend from the vitcom
比从wetpack
than from the wetpack
车
car
例如，它是一个
for example it is a
例如，在wetpack中，普遍承认的设计PT是
universally acknowledged design PT in wetpack that
它不应该在API中同时有负载和插头
it shouldn't have both the load and plug in API
因为这带来了两个问题
because this brings 2 problems
第一
first
用户可能不知道该使用哪个API
users might not know which API to use
有时他们甚至可能
sometimes they might even
一开始就选错了
have chosen the wrong one at first
比如es linksof loader
like the es linksof loader
后来被变成了es inter webpack pagan
was later turned into es inter webpack pagan
因为autos发现plagan的apis
because the autos found that the plagan apis
更适合于我们的使用情况和
are more suitable for the use case of usand
而有时
and sometimes
我们可能同时需要负载和
we may need both loads and
插件apis来实现一个单一的
the plugin apis to achieve one single
功能
functionality
这就是视图加载器的情况
that's the case for view loader
尽管它的名字里有世界加载器的字样
even though it has the world loader in its name
用户仍然需要使用视图加载器
users still have to use the view loader
攻击同一软件包中的出口
attacking export from the same package
与视图加载器一起
together with the view loader
来制作一个导出视图的单文件组件
to make an export view single file component
这些都不再是
these are no longer
在Viet和角色上的问题，因为
problems in Viet and the role up because
他们只有一种方式可以从时钟上扩展
they only have one way to extend from the clock
那就是插件系统
that's the plugin system
最后，关于小麦
lastly as of wheat
小麦的第三大创造
the 3rd major creation of wheat
我们相信，小麦已经足够成熟
we believe that wheat is mature
我们相信小麦已经足够成熟，并且已经为严肃的用例做好了准备
enough and more than ready for serious use cases
因为尽管它很简单
because with all its simplicity
它仍然有足够的力量调用
it still has a power enough call
它已准备好与许多内置的集成系统一起使用
it is ready for use with many built integrations
它使用滚动的战斗测试
it uses roll up the battle test
用于生产捆绑
for production bundling
当然，还有
and of course
超级性能的债务服务器是它的一个
the super performance debt server is one of its
最具代表性的功能
most iconic feature
嘿
hey
而且它默认启用了静态资产处理功能
and it has static assets handling enabled by default
不需要额外的用户考虑
no extra user consideration is required
所以这使得feat更像wetpack
so this makes feat more like wetpack
更像stui而不是webpack
more like stui than webpack
而
the
这也是我们改用feed的另一个原因
that's another reason for us to switch to feed
而不是创建另一个层
directly instead of creating another layer
而不是创建另一层，即卡片式的feed cri或其他东西
card feed cri or something else
而对于更复杂的用例
and for more sophisticated use cases
如兄弟的兼容性问题
such as brother compatibility issues
和单元测试解决方案
and unit testing solutions
Fitz已经有了一个丰富的生态系统
Fitz has already has a rich ecosystem
它有第一方插件
it has first party plugins
为圣经转述，它有第三方旅游
for bible transpiration and it has 3rd party tours
像适合测试的
like fit test for
单元测试
unit testings
因此，菲茨现在的功能是与
so fit is now in feature parity with
感受你的眼睛，主要是
feels your eye mostly
而且
and
这使我们对转换更有信心
that makes us more confident in a switching
这是一个混合的祝福，它是一个
it is a mixed blessing that it is a
它是一个全新一代的网络工具
completely new generation of web tools
我们可以利用这个机会采取不同的
we can take the opportunity to take a different
我们可以借此机会采取不同的方法来解决一些问题，而这些问题
approach of some of the issues that
是不可能的
wasn't possible
以前在pcl和y pack中是不可能的
previously in pcl and y pack
我们放弃了对许多反模式的关注
we dropped spot for many anti patterns
例如
for example
esm和cgs代码不再被允许混合使用
esm and cgs code are no longer allowed to be mixed
在用户项目中
in user projects
你不能使用模块
you cannot use module
输出和导入语句在同一模块中使用。
exports and import statements in the single
在同一个模块中使用
in the same module
当然，只允许使用cgs代码的依赖性
of course cgs only code are allowed in dependence
但
but
你的项目代码会因为这个限制而变得更干净
your project code will be cleaner with this limitation
至于视图的困扰
as of the view plaguing of it
我们现在强制要求
we now force
明确的扩展，当你从一个
explicit extensionswhen you import from a
的时候，我们会强制使用明确的扩展名，因为这样可以使
few single file components because that makes the
与其他工具的整合更容易
integration with other tools easier
要求，并且类型脚本可以识别
asking towards and the type script can recognize the
识别少数单一文件的组件
few single file components earlier
这在将来会减少问题。
and that would be less problematic in the future
适合不仅是
fit does not only
在技术问题上采取了不同的方法
take a different approach on technical issues
它还在许多层面上改善了项目的管理
it also improves the project management on many levels
它现在有一个可预测的发布套件
it now has a predictable release kit
这就是
that is
每年至少有一个主要的版本，这就是它的形状
it's what shapes at least one major version every year
以便与注释js版本保持一致
to be in line with note js versions
因此，每年都会有一个生命末期的版本出现。
so every year this would drop a spot for end of life
而不是js版本
not js versions
今年，Fitz jobs fit 3被删除
this year Fitz jobs fit 3 dropped
非礼服的位置12
spots for non dress 12
而明年的2023年
and next year 2023
适合非礼服14的下降支持
fits what dropped support for non dress 14
小规模的频繁和
the small frequent and
可预测的发布节奏
predictable release cadence
也使得
also makes
每个主要版本的迁移路径更加顺畅
the migration path of each major version smoother
它将有更少的
it will have fewer
破坏性变化
breaking changes in each major releases
所以你不会再看到
so you will no longer see
一长串的
the long list of
迁移指南中的一长串破坏性变化
breaking changes in the migration guide
而且这种
and this
迁移的便利性也得到了维塔公司的保证。
ease of migration is also guaranteed by the vita
生态系统cip库
ecosystem cip repository
每一个版本
with every release
适应性是通过所有主要参与者的测试
fit is tested with all is the major players
的主要参与者进行测试。
in the ecosystem
如果你正在使用vita
and if you are using vita
与一个包装器或一个隐喻或其他东西
with a wrapper or a metaphor or something else
它们将被
they will be
保证在发布前可以使用
guaranteed to be useable before the release
所以迁移的路径会更顺畅
so the migration pathis smoother
在从Bill CIA到Vita的过渡中
in a transition from Bill CIA to veet
我们还利用这个机会
we've also taken this opportunity
解除了一些复杂的功能
to decapo some complex features
从主工具中分离出来
from the main tool
在View Cri
in view cri
我们过去有概念性的颜色生成器
we used to have the concept color generators
是特殊的插件，用于
which are special plugins used to
创建或修改用户项目中的文件
create or modify files in a user project
这些生成器通常是
these generators are often
彼此紧密结合在一起
tightly coupled with each other
例如，类型脚本 begin
for example the type script begin
是用来
is used to
修改
modify
从coi服务包中创建的javascript文件
javascript files created from the coi service package
创建的javascript文件，但对
but has special handling for
创建的文件进行特殊处理。
files created from the
路由器插件
router plugin
所以这使得这些
so that makes these
生成器难以长期维护
generators hard to maintain in the long run
现在
now that
我们正在创建新的工具
we are creating new tools
所以我们决定创建一个专门的脚手架工具
so we decided to create a dedicated scaffolding tools
为每一个用例创建一个专门的脚手架工具
for each of these use cases
我们已经创建了一个视图
we have created a view
其中我有所有的
which I have all the
视图项目的基本必需品
basic necessities for our view project
和
and
对于那些使用自己的模板的人来说，他们使用的是
for those who are using their own templates are using
所有基于网络包的项目
all the web pack based projects
我们有几个
we have thefew
斜线在冲突包中创建，用于
slash creates in the conflict package that are used
只用于为你创建我们的链接配置
for only creating the us link configurations for you
如果你想拥有自己的项目模板
and if you want to have your own project template
我认为这是一个不错的选择
I think it is a good choice to
如果你想拥有你自己的项目模板，我认为这是一个很好的选择，创建github仓库作为模板并使用
create github repositories as templates and use
门来为你下载这些模板。
the gates to download these templates for you
视图服务中的另一种类型的插件服务插件
another type of plugin in view service service plugins
这些都是用来扩展web back的插件。
these are plugins used to extend the web back
冲突，从
conflict from the
调用coi服务和coi插件
call coi service and coi plugins
现在，这个节拍更容易配置和扩展了
now that beat is easier to configure and extend from
呃，我们不再需要另一个抽象层了，所以
uh we no longer need another layer of abstractions so
我们不再需要另一个抽象层，因此，不再需要封一个服务园
no more seal a service park in
你可以只在项目中使用普通的珠子。
you can just use plain bead bargains in a project
好了，现在让我们仔细看看每个珊瑚的
okay now let's take a closer look at each of the coral
填补coi插件，看看
fill coi plugins and see
我们在脚下的生态系统里有什么？
what we've got in the feet ecosystem
首先让我们从Yes Clint插件开始
first let's start with the yes Clint plugin
yeastint pagan是用来帮助用户
the yeastint pagan was used to help users
配置yeastint
configure yeastints
在他们的项目中，并
in their projects and
在项目编译过程中链接
linked the
文件在项目编译过程中
files during project compilation
为配置路径
for the configuration path
我们已经创建了一个新的旅游，你可以调用
we've created a new tour and you can call the
创建一些斜线的小配置。
mpn create a few slash yes little config
来帮助你在面试项目中配置是的
to help youconfigure yes in interview projects
呃，包括配合
uh that includes fits
不仅在配合项目中，而且在
not only in fit projects but also in
网络包项目和或在
web pack projects and or in
uh 一些ci项目
uh few ci projects
至于项目编译过程中的链接部分
as for the linking during project compilation parts
我们现在发现
we now find
我们现在发现，这并不是一个理想的链接方式，因为
that it is not the ideal way to do linking because
它损害了编译性能
it hurts the compilation performance
和
and
大多数想法和编辑
most ideas and editors
在停车位上有，所以
have yes in the parking so
我们不建议你只使用你的id
we not recommend you to just use your id
或编辑功能
or editor feature
来使用升级，而不是
to use the escalate instead of
使用捆绑的插件
use a bundle of plugin
而至于顶部的脚本则是
and as for the top script bargain
的转换
transformation of
TS文件是默认支持的，在适合
TS files are supported by default in fit
在es build的帮助下
with help of es build
如果你想进行类型检查
if you want type checking
我们也建议你使用你的
we also recommend you to use the integrations of your
编辑器或
editors or
和IGES
iges and
如果你想在命令行中进行类型检查，那么
if you want to do the type check in command line then
你可以安装votsc
you can install the votsc
包。
package separately
当然，如果你确实想看到
of course if you do want to see the
链接和类型检查的结果
linking and types checking results
在你的浏览器页面上实时显示
in your browser page in real time
有1个
there is 1/3 party
null
plugin called wheat plugging checker
that runs these tools
null
in our walker thread
which is non blocking
null
and the result will be shown in the
plaza era of a lake
null
just like what we've got in the UCI in the past
as for the unit's testing solutions
null
actually we are not satisfied with any of our
previous solutions
null
Jesse is a great tool
um but the biggest
null
problem of it is that it doesn't
share confusions with the bandala
null
it has its own ecosystem of
transformers and resolves
null
and
users have to maintain a standard long configuration
null
files just for just itself
and the testing environment might
null
end up not the same as the project
execution context
null
so that's not ideal
mocha is another great tool
null
but it is tedious
to configure mocha to make it work with other bundles
null
the mocha pack
mostly used
null
mocha integration with web pack
takes much time to
null
upgrade to web pack
and it still hasn't upgraded to mocha 10 yet
null
luckily we now have v test which is a feat based
unit testing tool so it's fast
null
by default and the
configurations of v test
null
is derived from the vs configuration
so the users runs other codes in a similar environment
null
and most importantly
it is well maintained
null
by people who are familiar with vit
所以更容易升级到新的Vit版本
so it's easier to upgrade to new vit versions
而且它也是维生素生态系统的一部分。
and it is also part of the vit ecosystem ci
如此多的生态系统
so much for the ecosystem
展望细节整合的未来
looking into the future of detail integration
我们仍有许多令人兴奋的新闻计划
we still have many exciting news things planned
例如，这是一个常见的错误来源，即可能有多个视图副本。
for example it is a common source of bug that there
可能会有一个以上的视图副本
may be more than one view copies
在同一个笔记模块中
in the same note modules
所以我们想默认推导出视图包
so we want to deduce the view package by default
并只保留一个副本
and keep only one copy of it
我们希望在Daryl测试之后再推出这个功能。
we'd like to ship this feature after Daryl testing
这是另一个潜在的改进
and here's another potential improvement
仿佛它鼓励尽可能地使用是的模块
as though it encourages yes modules whenever possible
可能有一些遗留的包
there may be some legacy packages
是以山寨版的格式发货的
that were shipped in the cottage s format
而它们甚至可能需要
and they might even require the
视图的普通版本，所以我们要改进这种
common dress version of view so we want to improve that
种包
kind of package
是一个可中断的新包
is an interruptability with newer packages
而且我们想在视图插件中做一些事情
and we want to do something
在视图插件中帮助改善这种情况
in a view plugin to help improve this situation
我们希望在视图插件中做一些事情来帮助改善这种情况，因为它已经非常快了。
slove it is already very fast
总是有改进的余地
there is always room for improvement
而且我们不会停止寻找方法来
and we won't stop looking for ways to
进一步加快脚步
speed up feet even further
我的演讲到此结束
so that's it for my talk
谢谢你的聆听
thank you for listening
希望你喜欢用视图和壮举进行编码，谢谢
hope you enjoy coding with view and feat thanks